<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Cannibal Meals (VGP required)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CannibalMeals.VGP</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/VGCannibalPatch</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>dismarzero.VGP.VGPVegetableGarden</packageId>
      <displayName>VGP Vegetable Garden</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2007061826</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=36926.0</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>dismarzero.VGP.VGPGardenGourmet</packageId>
      <displayName>VGP Garden Gourmet</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2007062982</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=36926.msg378130#msg378130</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>dismarzero.VGP.VGPVegetableGarden</li>
    <li>dismarzero.VGP.VGPGardenGourmet</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
  
Adds cannibal versions of [strike]all base and[/strike] Vegetable Garden Project-meals.

General
[list]
[*]Add these recipes/meals: Stir-Fry, Stew, Pizza, Salted Meat, Cheeseburger, Tacos, Meat Pie, Kabobs, Grilled Steak
[*]Has added texture on the original textures to indicate cannibal-version.
[*]Stats and nutritions are the same as the original meals.
[*]Adds a Cannibal meal category for sorting.
[/list]

Compatibilities
[list]
[*]Compatible with existing saves and other mods.
[*]Requires Vegetable Garden Project + VGP Gourmet and should be loaded after those two
[/list]

 For helping with translations, please see the github-link above.

If dismarzero (VPG owner) wants to publish this as a separate VGP I'll gladly take this down and send over the files.
This is originally an expansion of Tremeloe's Cook Cannibal Meal (IndividualStack) 
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1297883744 that has not been updated to 1.0 yet. This mod also adds Tremeloe's meals to the VGP Food Prep-table.

[h1]Update[/h1]
To simplify my mod-updating and improve this mod I have chosen to remove the cannibal vanilla-meals in this mod. This mod was primarly intended as a patch for VGP and since I already have a mod that adds cannibal versions of vanilla meals that also has support for other mods structures and races I think its better if these two mods can be used side by side instead.
If you have vanilla-type cannibal meals in your save that you would like to keep, please subscribe to my other mod and reload your save as it uses the same meal-definitions as this mod used.
Cannibal and Insect Meals
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1558455017

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/VGCannibalPatch][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>